

# **AKANKSHA SINGH**

Infosys Limited, (Senior Associate Consultant)

# **PROFILE**

I am a professional SAP Consultant with over 5 years of experience in SAP and cross module integration. Seeking to obtain a challenging position with an organization that encourages independent thinking and allows me to drive conceptual and creative framework while staying true to the company's core values.

#### CONTACT ME



9137472922



singhakankshav@gmail.com



Kalyan, Mumbai.

## **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

#### MUMBAI UNIVERSITY

Master of Commerce (May 2015- May 2017) Specialization in Accountancy

# JAI BHAGWAN COLLEGE OF **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Education (July 2015 - April 2017)

# K. J. SOMAIYA COLLEGE OF ARTS AND COMMERCE

Bachelor of Commerce (July 2012 - April 2015)

## SKI LLS

- SAP FICO
- · Financial Accounting
- · Positive Attitude & Good managerial skills
- · Ready to take responsibilities
- Quick Learner & Approachable
- · Proficient at building & maintaining professional relationships.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Infosys Ltd., Associate Consultant (September 2022 - Till Present)

#### Working on S/4 Hana for Manufacturing Client.

- Working on Enhancements and support for assets, banking and integration module.
- Managing the cross functional ER's and co ordinating with multiple teams.
- · Handling client call and leading the same based on their requirements.

#### Worked on S/4 Hana 1605 Support for Pharma Client.

- · Giving support for NASA region.
- · Completed mandatory company as well as project specific trainings.
- · Resolving all day-to-day issues related to Master Data, Cost center.
- · Working on FI-MM-SD Integration.
- Handling month end reporting.
- Interaction with business to ensure proper understanding of the business requirements and Functional specifications.

## Capgemini Pvt Ltd., Associate Consultant (May 2019 - August 2022)

## Worked on S/4 Hana 1605 Support for Manufacturing Client.

- · Given support for all over EMEA region.
- · Performed daily monitoring for exchange rate.
- Performed weekly monitoring for depreciation Jobs and Idoc.
- Provided assistance, investigated & resolved user problems wherever possible, in the area of FI, AR, AP, GL and FI-MM-SD.
- Worked on Master Data Creation and have good knowledge on Fiscal year variant, Field status group, posting period, GL master, cost center, IDoc, Asset Accounting, Bank, Dunning and tax.
- Configured areas of AP, House banks and Automatic Payment Program.
- Creation of New company code for operating RE-FX module in SAP.
- Worked on data migration via LSMW.
- Managed incidents tickets per service level agreements, works on root cause analysis and corrective actions.
- Handled month end and year end activities efficiently.
- Completed Capgemini internal SAP FICO certification successfully.
- Received average score from client 9.5/10.

# Swami Vivekanand High School and Junior College, Teacher (June 2017 - March 2019

- · Handling the strength of 63 students.
- · Keeping the records of every work done.
- Conducted the cultural programs & taking care of HR responsibilities.

# STRENGTHS

- · Always open to learn new things and implement those.
- · Believe in never giving up mentality.
- Good confidence level, presentation and communication skills.
- · Commitment towards work.

# **AWARDS**

- STAR (Special Thanks and Recognition) Awards Q3 2021
- STAR (Special Thanks and Recognition) Awards Q1 2021
- Received Support award for giving assistance and co operation towards various activities during academic year.

# **EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

- · Participated in physical fitness challenge and won it.
- Actively participated in other activities during lockdown and also got rewarded for the same.
- · Member of Cultural Committee.
- · Participation in various college activities.
- · Participation in Quiz Competition.

## EXTERNAL CANDIDATE

**Singh, Akanksha** 9137472922 singhakankshav@gmail.com